Guide to the Louise Degn broadcast journalism audio-visual collection 1969-2007
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- KSL news, Maggie Smith essays and cooking - Louise Degn, producer, 1984; 1986; DVD (Disc 14)
  - Maggie Smith obituary, 1986 January 28 (Video 1)
    Louise Degn's note: Maggie Smith did cooking segments and personal essays on "Good Company/Good Friends," a daytime talk show on KSL-TV. Maggie was joyful and eccentric. For example, for years she told people she was 80-years-old, even though when she died, she was only 77. She thought 80 had "character." She appeared from Feb. 1984 until her death in Jan. 1986. This was actually her second stint as a KSL personality. Years before, in the 1940s and 1950s, she had a program on KSL Radio under the name, Margaret Masters. I remember listening to it as a child. She did a mix of recipes, household tips, gossip, and good neighbor talk that was popular on radio stations across the country at that time. Her warm personality that made her a popular radio host and it carried over to television when we resurrected her career on TV. Louise Degn, producer. Kerry Jensen, principle photographer. Shelley Osterloh, host.
  - Maggie Smith - boyfriends forgotten, 1984 February 21 (Video 2)
    04:30.
  - Maggie Smith - Baxter Jones, 1984 February 28 (Video 3)
    03:38.
  - Maggie Smith - gluttony, 1984 March 06 (Video 4)
    03:10.
  - Maggie Smith - bread - cooking, 1984 March 05 (Video 5)
    05:29.
  - Maggie Smith - cracking eggs, 1984 March 13 (Video 6)
    00:55.
  - Maggie Smith - fried bananas - cooking, 1984 March 16 (Video 7)
    02:57.
  - Maggie Smith - happy marriage, 1984 March 20 (Video 8)
    01:48.
  - Maggie Smith - cheese cake - cooking, 1984 March 23 (Video 9)
    04:06.
  - Maggie Smith - cinnamon rolls - cooking, 1984 March 30 (Video 10)
    04:15.
  - Maggie Smith - red shoes, 1984 April 03 (Video 11)
    01:18.
  - Maggie Smith - kid's drawings, 1984 April 17 (Video 12)
  - Maggie Smith - three-faced doll, 1984 May 07 (Video 13)
    01:06.
  - Maggie Smith - mashed potatoes - cooking, 1984 May 04 (Video 14)
    04:39.
  - Maggie Smith - vase, 1984 May 14 (Video 15)
  - Maggie Smith - refrigerator, 1984 May 18 (Video 16)
    02:44.
  - Maggie Smith - three chins, 1984 May 21 (Video 17)
    01:17.
  - Maggie Smith - grandfather's barn, 1984 June 11 (Video 18)
    01:11.
  - Maggie Smith - shyness, 1984 June 25 (Video 19)
    01:37.
  - Maggie Smith - Jerry Steinblek, 1984 July 02 (Video 20)
  - Maggie Smith - stung by a bee, 1984 July 09 (Video 21)
    01:47.
  - Maggie Smith - being single, 1984 July (Video 22)
    02:10.
  - Maggie Smith - Mrs. Tremelo, circa 1984 (Video 23)
    Unaired. 02:30.
- KSL news, Maggie Smith and Elouise Bell essays and cooking - Louise Degn, producer, 1984-1985; DVD (Disc 15)
  - Maggie Smith - Lillie Mae's husbands, 1985 (Video 1)
  - Maggie Smith - Temperance Lee, 1985 (Video 2)
    01:34.
  - Maggie Smith - Brucie and his dog, 1985 (Video 3)
    01:32.
  - Maggie Smith - advice for Eric, 1985 (Video 3)
    01:28.
  - Maggie Smith - mother's habit, 1985 (Video 4)
  - Maggie Smith - nice to kids, 1985 (Video 5)
    02:00.
  - Maggie Smith - lilac bushes, 1985 (Video 6)
    01:23.
  - Maggie Smith - getting good help, 1985 (Video 7)
  - Maggie Smith - strawberry Pie - cooking, 1985 (Video 8)
    05:00.
  - Elouise Bell - hospital tests, 1984 (Video 9)
    01:44.
    Louise Degn's note: Elouise Bell taught English at Brigham Young University from 1963 – 1994. She was a popular humor writer. These essays were adopted from her writings. From 1984 to 1985 she appeared on "Good Company/Good Friends," a day-time talk show on KSL-TV. Louise Degn, producer.
  - Elouise Bell - operation, 1984 (Video 10)
    01:40.
  - Elouise Bell - zucchini 1, 1984 (Video 11)
    01:49.
  - Elouise Bell - zucchini 2, 1984 (Video 12)
    01:30.
  - Elouise Bell - family reunion, 1984 (Video 13)
  - Elouise Bell - trivia, 1984 (Video 14)
    01:39.
  - Elouise Bell - color coding, 1984 (Video 15)
    01:22.
  - Elouise Bell - student writing, 1984 (Video 16)
    01:16.
  - Elouise Bell - traveling in Utah, 1984 (Video 17)
  - Elouise Bell - disappearing things, 1984 (Video 18)
    01:50.
  - Elouise Bell - visitors check list, 1984 (Video 19)
    02:22.
  - Elouise Bell - food exercises, 1984 (Video 20)
    02:02.
  - Elouise Bell - house guests, 1984 (Video 21)
  - Elouise Bell - family fights, 1984 (Video 22)
    02:14.
  - Elouise Bell - TV chefs, 1984 (Video 23)
  - Elouise Bell - habits, 1984 (Video 24)
  - Elouise Bell - bikers, 1984 (Video 25)
    01:36.
  - Elouise Bell - therapists, 1984 (Video 26)
  - Elouise Bell - extra zucchini, 1984 (Video 27)
  - Elouise Bell - homework, 1984 (Video 28)
    02:07.
- KSL news, TalkAbout interview shows - Louise Degn, producer, 1985-1986; DVD (Disc 16)
  - MTV's effect on children promo, 1985 October 03 (Video 1)
  - MTV's effect on children, 1985 October 03 (Video 2)
    Influence of music videos on children's behavior. 24:45.
  - Disciplining children, 1985 October 07 (Video 3)
    Psychologist Lynn Scoresby gives advice to parents. 21:15.
  - Disciplining children, 1986 November 14 (Video 3)
  - Family series, 1986 November 14 (Video 4)
    Summary of 15 shows on the changing family: single adoptions, working mothers, househusbands, blended families, generational changes in families. 22:50.
- KSL news, arol Lynn Pearson and Carlfred Broderick interviews - Louise Degn, producer, 1986; DVD (Disc 17)
  - Carol Lynn Pearson - 10PM news story, 1986 August 20 (Video 1)
    02:11.
  - Carol Lynn Pearson - Prime Time Access (Video 2)
    09:25.
  - Carol Lynn Pearson - TalkAbout (Video 3)
    Mormon author cares for homosexual husband with Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome (AIDS). 22:50.
  - Carlfred Broderick - TalkAbout (Video 4)
    Mormon family therapist discusses family relationships. 23:10.
- KSL Dimension Five, 1986; DVD (Disc 18)
  - Final show, 1986 September 13 (Video 1)
    26:30.
  - Early show opens and sets, 1986 September 13 (Video 2)
    03:20.
  - Interview with Ed Yeates, first executive producer, 1986 September 13 (Video 3)
    Includes story excerpts: Roller Coaster Maker, Arrow-Huss Co., Clearfield, UT (Ed Yeates, reporter), Actor Tony Geary of North Summit High School (Holly McCullom, reporter), F-16 jet computers, Hill Air Force Base (Steve Connelly, reporter). 08:27.
  - Bedroom Gold Miner, Chris Christopherson, Murray, ID, 1986 September 13 (Video 4)
    Holly McCullom, reporter. 04:28.
  - Bloopers, 1986 September 13 (Video 5)
    01:29.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Southern Exposure series - Louise Degn, producer, 1987; DVD (Disc 19)
  - Arches National Park, 1987 May 18 (Video 1)
    Moab Jeep safari (Karl Peterson, photographer), Moab Dump (Bruce Lindsay, reporter), Ancient Pack Rats in Canyonlands (Ed Yeates, reporter), How Arches Were Formed. Interview with Ranger Steve Swanke (1:52), Delicate Arch Marriage of Alec Wilkins and Cheryl Sue Christensen (Sam Prigg, photographer). 21:00.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Southern Exposure series - Louise Degn, producer, 1987; DVD (Disc 20)
  - Monument Valley, 1987 May 19 (Video 1)
    John Ford, movie director (Chris Hicks, reporter), Navajo Marina (Keith McCord, reporter), Navajo High School (Alexis Fernandez, reporter), Green Mask, Grand Gulch, Anasazi Cave (Duane Cardall, reporter). 22:30.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Southern Exposure series - Louise Degn, producer, 1987; DVD (Disc 21)
  - Lake Powell, 1987 May 19 (Video 1)
    Water Skier, Richard Briggs, attempting a record 1,900 miles, Glen Canyon Dam economics (John Hollenhorst, reporter), Perry Lodge in Kanab, Utah (Keith McCord, reporter. Not on DVD). 19:10.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Southern Exposure series - Louise Degn, producer, 1987; DVD (Disc 22)
  - Bryce Canyon, 1987 May 21 (Video 1)
    Burr Trail Commuter, Marjie Spencer (Alexis Fernandez, reporter), Kodachrome Basin State Park (Keith McCord, reporter), The Donut Priest, Father Joseph Valine (Duane Cardall, reporter), Mysterious Loa Bulge (Ed Yeates, reporter). 21:45.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Southern Exposure series - Louise Degn, producer, 1987; DVD (Disc 23)
  - Great Basin National Park, 1987 May 22 (Video 1)
    Lehman Cave (Ed Yeates, reporter), Baker, Nevada (Alexis Fernandez, reporter), Callao, Utah, one-room schoolhouse (Allison Barlow, reporter), Small Museums and Shops (Keith McCord, reporter).Tooele County Museum, PreHistoric Museum, College of Eastern Utah, Price, Beaver County Courthouse, Millard County Chronicle Office, Delta (two-headed sheep), Edge of the Cedars Museum, Blanding (Anasazi artifacts), Joseph Smith Profile Rock, Millard County, Territorial Statehouse, Fillmore, Old Rock Church, Parowan, Hole in the Rock, Moab. 21:00.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Autumn Leave series - Louise Degn, producer, 1987; DVD (Disc 24)
  - Rural Idaho, 1987 September 21 (Video 1)
    Airborne mail carrier, Ray Arnold, Cascade, ID (Keith McCord, reporter), Town's only nurse, Marie Osborn, Stanley, ID (Allison Barlow, reporter), Montage of western locales visited on Prime Time Access, Custom fishing rod maker, Alton Wilde, Rexburg, ID (Don Olsen, reporter). 23:20.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Autumn Leave series - Louise Degn, producer, 1987; DVD (Disc 25)
  - Jackson Hole, Wyoming, 1987 September 22 (Video 1)
    Mountain Climbing School (Karl Petersen, photographer), Gerry Spence, defense attorney (Alexis Fernandez, reporter), Should wolves be reintroduced into Yellowstone/Jackson? (John Hollenhorst, reporter). 21:00.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Autumn Leave series - Louise Degn, producer, 1987; DVD (Disc 26)
  - Bear Lake, 1987 September 23 (Video 1)
    Raspberries, Hilt and Price Family Farms (Shelley Thomas, reporter), Post Office moving to new building, St. Charles, ID (Duane Cardall, reporter), Economic development around lake (Dave Thomas, reporter), Rural Life, video essay (Greg Sumner, photographer). 20:30.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Autumn Leave series - Louise Degn, producer, 1987; DVD (Disc 27)
  - Heber Valley, 1987 September 24 (Video 1)
    Homestead Resort turns 101 (Duane Cardall, reporter), Hot Pots (Ed Yeates, reporter), Jordanelle Dam controversy (John Hollenhorst, reporter), Cascade Springs, video essay (Bob Greenwell, photographer). 21:20.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Autumn Leave series - Louise Degn, producer, 1987; DVD (Disc 28)
  - Flaming Gorge, 1987 September 25 (Video 1)
    Sonar trout fishing with Steve Wolstenhulm (Don Judd, reporter), Ute Mountain Lookout Tower, Ashley National Forest: the last remaining fire look-out tower in Utah (Alexis Fernandez, reporter), Fontenelle Dam on Green River in Wyoming is leaking (John Hollenhorst, reporter), Bloopers. 20:40.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access documentary - Louise Degn, producer, 1987; DVD (Disc 29)
  - No Home for the Holidays, 1987 December 14 (Video 1)
    Who are the homeless? (Bruce Lindsay, reporter), Police and the homeless (Sam Prigg, photographer/producer), One woman's path to homelessness (Alexis Fernandez, reporter), Community activist, Steve Holbrook, on building a homeless shelter in Salt Lake City (Duane Cardall, reporter). 21:40.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Sunspots series - Louise Degn, producer, 1988; DVD (Disc 30)
  - Hawaii part 1, 1988 February 15 (Video 1)
    Where Utahns travel in winter (Keith McCord, reporter), TV shows filmed in Hawaii (Louise Degn, field producer), Volcanos (Ed Yeates, reporter). 22:30.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Sunspots series - Louise Degn, producer, 1988; DVD (Disc 31)
  - Hawaii part 2, 1988 February 16 (Video 1)
    Polynesian Cultural Center Tour in Llai'e, Iosepa, Mormon Polynesian settlement in Skull Valley, UT (Bruce Lindsay, reporter), The ecology of the Manoa Valley rain forest (Ed Yeates, reporter). 20:00.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Sunspots series - Louise Degn, producer, 1988; DVD (Disc 32)
  - Hawaii part 3, 1988 February 17 (Video 1)
    Mrs. Fields's Cookies has kahoona bless new store location, Movies filmed in Polynesia (Chris Hicks, reporter), Observatory on Mauna Kea Peak (Ed Yeates, reporter), Utahns who work in pineapple groves (Dave Block, field producer). 21:00.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access documentary - Louise Degn, producer, 1988; DVD (Disc 33)
  - Lost Love, 1988 February 23 (Video 1)
    Divorce: Lee and Jared Willis, father and son (Shelley Thomas, reporter), "I Cried" music video (Sam Prigg, photographer), Child's death: Dale and Marsha Stroup, parents (Alexis Fernandez, reporter). 21:30.
    Louise Degn's note: This program won an Emmy Award. Shelley Thomas, anchor. Marybeth Raynes, LCSW.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Highway 91 series - Louise Degn, producer, 1988; DVD (Disc 34)
  - Idaho border through Ogden, 1988 May 16 (Video 1)
    Smithfield Implement Co (Don Olsen, reporter), Bluebird Café (Alexis Fernandez, reporter), Dr. Pierce's sign, Wellsville, Mantua, Utah ( Dave Thompson, reporter), Ogden Cops, Lt. Richard Peterson (Larry Lewis, reporter). 21:30.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Highway 91 series - Louise Degn, producer, 1988; DVD (Disc 35)
  - Davis County through Utah County, 1988 May 17 (Video 1)
    Deseret Mill, Kaysville, Slim Olsen's gas station, Bountiful (Bruce Lindsay, reporter), Teenagers Drag State Street, Salt Lake City (Keith McCord, reporter), Lehi Roller Mills, Lehi, Timpanogos Cave, Ranger Arlo Shelley (Duane Cardall, reporter), Pioneer Drive In Movie Theater, Provo (Ed Yeates, reporter). 20:30.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Highway 91 series - Louise Degn, producer, 1988; DVD (Disc 36)
  - Juab County through Millard County, 1988 May 18 (Video 1)
    Mona Beekeeper, Greg Newton (Allison Barlow, reporter), Kay's Market in Mona, Utah, Dan Valentine Cafe Books, Death Strip, Highway 91 near Levan (Bob Walz, reporter), Scipio Bus Driver, Carolyn Memmot (Alexis Fernandez, reporter), Pioneer Statehouse, Filmore, Kanosh Baseball (Keith McCord, reporter). 21:00.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Highway 91 series - Louise Degn, producer, 1988; DVD (Disc 37)
  - Beaver County through Iron County, 1988 May 19 (Video 1)
    Cove Fort, Utah, Volcanos on Central Utah (Ed Yeates, reporter), High School Radio Station in Beaver, Utah, The Beaver Weekly Press (Bruce Lindsay, reporter), Beaver Bakery. Annie Stapley and Jenny Gale, sisters, LaSpina Arts Group. Cary and Stevi LaSpina (Carole Mikita, reporter), Paragonah General Store, Parowan, Utah Cafe (Shelley Osterloh, reporter). 21:00.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access, Highway 91 series - Louise Degn, producer, 1988; DVD (Disc 38)
  - Washington County to Arizona border, 1988 May 20 (Video 1)
    Cedar City, Utah, Kolob Canyon, Leeds Cookbook by Cecelia Ludwig (Allison Barlow, reporter), Silver Reef Monument, artist Jerry Andersen, Quail Creek Reservoir, Cotton Festival in Washington, Utah, Fitness Institute in Snow Canyon (Shelley Osterloh, reporter), Tortoise Man, Russell Bezette, of LaVerkin, Utah (Duane Cardall, reporter), Archie Bell, owner of 1957 Chevrolet. 21:25.
- KSL news, Prime Time Access final show - Louise Degn, producer, 1988; DVD (Disc 39)
  - Final show, 1988 August 26 (Video 1)
    Clips from first show 20 Sept 1982, Bruce Lindsay anchor, Candy Dish 5 given to viewer Ruth Hawkins, Reporter Memories from Ed Yeates, Alexis Fernandez, Keith McCord, Shelley Thomas, Chris Hicks, Osmond kids singing "Bye, Bye, Bruce," Bloopers including: Keith McCord with Jay Leno, early Carole Mikita, John Hollenhorst at the beauty parlor, Art Linkletter telling McCord to shave his moustache, Bruce Lindsay shaving his beard, Gina Stucki, "Don't Worry, Be Happy" music video. Brad Pearson, editor. 22:00.
- KSL documentary, Lowell Bennion - Louise Degn, producer, 1992; DVD (Disc 40)
  - Lowell Bennion: a life that matters, 1992 September 02 (Video 1)
    Documentary. 23:30.
    Louise Degn's note: When I left full-time employment at KSL, I felt I left two unfinished projects: 1) an archive of historic work of which this DVD is a part and 2) a documentation of the life of Lowell Bennion. I was able to complete the Bennion project for KSL as a free-lance producer two years after leaving KSL full-time. I wanted to include his wife and all five children to show the impact public service has on private life. At the time of the interview, Lowell Bennion was 84 and frail, though mentally sharp. He died in February 1996 at age 87.
  - LDS General Conference talk, 1968 April (Video 2)
    27:00.
  - Howard Bennion, son, excerpt 1 (Video 3)
    02:35.
  - Ben Bennion, son (Video 4)
    03:40.
  - Doug Bennion, son (Video 5)
    01:05.
  - Ellen Bennion Stone, daughter (Video 6)
    01:00.
  - Steve Bennion, son (Video 7)
  - Howard Bennion, son, excerpt 2 (Video 8)
  - Mary Bradford, biographer (Video 8)
    39:00.
- KUED docuemtnary - Louise Degn and Marie Cornwall, producers, 1995; DVD (Disc 41)
  - Utah women considered, 1995 March 28 (Video 1)
    How lives of women have changed in 20th Century. 57:00.
    Louise Degn's note: This program won Best of Show and a Commendation Award (Gracie) from the American Women in Radio and Television in 1996.
- KUED docuemtnary - Louise Degn and Nancy Green, producers, 1997; DVD (Disc 42)
  - Let the women vote!, 1997 July 06 (Video 1)
    Woman suffrage in Wyoming, Utah, Colorado, Idaho. 56:40.
    Louise Degn's note: This program won the following awards: National distribution, PBS stations - The program was aired in over 50 cities including New York City, Philadelphia, Washington, Minneapolis, San Francisco, Austin, Nashville, Milwaukee, Phoenix, Orlando, and others (1999), Selected for Showing at Museum of Broadcasting, Chicago - "Significant Documentaries Exploring the 20th Century" and inclusion in permanent archive (1998), Gracie - American Women in Radio and Television, TV Documentary (1998), 1st Place - Broadcast Education Association, Juried Faculty Production Competition, TV Documentary (1998).
- Volunteer summit brodcast on all Utah stations - Louise Degn, producer, 1997; DVD (Disc 43)
  - Volunteer summit, 1997 October 22 (Video 1)
    Gov. Mike Leavitt and Gen. Colin Powell urge volunteers to aid troubled youth. 27:25.
- KUER radio news stories - Louise Degn, reporter, 2000-2002; DVD (Disc 44)
  - School of the Natural Order, 2000 June 15 (Video 1)
    A spiritual community founded in 1957 outside Baker, Nevada by Ralph "Vitvan" deBit still has a hand-full of residents. 9:00.
  - Mormon History Association in Denmark, 2000 August 01 (Video 2)
    150th anniversary of the Mormon Church in continental Europe. 7:55.
  - Spiritual Directors movements, 2000 November 28 (Video 3)
    Lay people counsel others on spiritual matters. 7:30.
  - Crones Counsel, 2002 March 25 (Video 4)
    Women age 50+ gather to share their life stories. 4:35.
  - Yard Sale music, 2002 March 25 (Video 5)
    Music historian Lynn Carson collects "vanity recordings" which document social and cultural trends. 9:30.
- KSL news, Jackie Nokes interviews - Ricki Rafner, producer, 1982-1986; DVD (Disc 45)
  - Holly Near, Bay Area singer/songwriter 1, 1982 March 04 (Video 1)
    04:37.
  - Holly Near, Bay Area singer/songwriter 2, 1982 March 04 (Video 2)
    25:25.
  - Jim Scott, Bay Area singer/songwriter, 1985 January (Video 2)
    03:50.
  - Hunter Davis, Bay Area singer/songwriter, 1986 May 01 (Video 3)
- KSL station history, 1984-2006; DVD (Disc 46)
  - KSL moves from Social Hall Avenue to Triad Center, 1984 April 13 (Video 1)
    03:44.
  - Paul James, sports anchor, retires, 1989 June 30 (Video 2)
  - Bob Welti, weathercaster, retires, 1991 Spring (Video 3)
  - Shelley Thomas, news anchor, retires, 1991 November 27 (Video 4)
    04:50.
  - Salt Lake stations switch network affiliation, 1994 (Video 5)
  - Mark Eubank, weathercaster, retires, 2006 November 29 (Video 6)
    Includes complete 10 p.m. newscast with commercials. 34:56.
- KSL-TV turns 40, 1989; DVD (Disc 47)
  - KSL turns 40, 1989 June 04 (Video 1)
    47:10.
- KSL-TV turns 50, 1999; DVD (Disc 48)
  - KSL turns 50 part 1, 1999 May 26 (Video 1)
    Includes complete 10 p.m. newscast with commercials. 37:43.
- KSL-TV turns 50, 1999; DVD (Disc 49)
  - KSL turns 50 part 2, 1999 June 01 (Video 1)
    59:43.
- Dick Norse, news anchor, retires, 2007; DVD (Disc 50)
  - Dick Nourse tribute program, 2007 November 28 (Video 1)
    27:20.
  - Dick Nourse final broadcast, 2007 November 28 (Video 2)
    Last 10 p.m. newscast, includes commercials. 35:35.
- KSL Studios attacked by gunwoman part 1, 1999; DVD (Disc 51)
  - 5 p.m. newscast, includes commercials, 1999 January 14 (Video 1)
    An armed woman, De Keiu Duy, attacks KSL station and kills AT&T employee, Anne Sleater. 31:22.
- KSL Studios attacked by gunwoman part 2, 1999; DVD (Disc 52)
  - 6:00 p.m. and 6:30 p.m. newscasts, includes commercials, 1999 January 14 (Video 1)
    An armed woman, De Keiu Duy, attacks KSL station and kills AT&T employee, Anne Sleater. 57:05.
- Utah historic events, 1983-1997; DVD (Disc 53)
  - Newhouse Hotel building demolition (KUTV), 1983 June 26 (Video 1)
    01:04.
  - Great Salt Lake rising (CBS), 1986 May 25 (Video 2)
    11:30.
  - Christmas Lights on Temple Square (KSL), circa 1980s (Video 3)
    Peter Semelka, photographer. 03:20.
  - Yellowstone Park fires (KUTV), 1988 September 07 (Video 4)
    07:15.
  - San Francisco earthquake (KSL), 1989 October 17 (Video 5)
    08:50.
  - Alta View hostage siege (KSL), 1991 September 21 (Video 6)
    09:45.
  - Wagon Train accident (KTVX), 1997 July 21 (Video 7)
    03:37.
  - Wagon Train accident (KSL), 1997 July 21 (Video 8)
  - Wagon Train accident (KSL), 1997 July 21 (Video 9)
    06:13.
- Perre Dale Selby execution, 1987; DVD (Disc 54)
  - KTVX 7:25 am newscast, Phil Reisen, reporter, 1987 August 28 (Video 1)
    02:38.
  - KTVX 5:30 pm newscast, Phil Reisen, reporter, 1987 August 28 (Video 2)
    07:00.
  - KUTV 6 pm newscast, Michael Rawson, reporter, 1987 August 28 (Video 3)
    06:00.
  - KSL 6 pm and 6:30 pm newscasts, 1987 August 28 (Video 4)
    31:20.
- Olympics coverage, 1994-1995; DVD (Disc 55)
  - Utah athletes compete at Winter Games in Norway, 1994 February 14 (Video 1)
    Reporters Bruce Lindsay, Shelley Osterloh, weathercaster Len Randolph. 20:00.
  - Salt Lake City awarded 2002 Winter Olympics, 1995 June 16 (Video 2)
    Reporters Bruce Lindsay, John Hollenhorst, Shelley Osterloh, Ruth Todd, Keith McCord, Deborah Lindner, Carole Mikita, Steve Eager, Craig Bollerjack. 53:33.
- Mormon Church national coverage, 1979-1987; DVD (Disc 56)
  - Garm Baum versus Mormon Church (CBS News 60 Minutes), 1979 December 09 (Video 1)
    Utah County cherry processor accuses LDS Church of bankrupting him. 13:40.
  - Unaired rebuttal to Garn Baum Story (Bonneville International), 1979 December 09 (Video 2)
    25:49.
  - AIDS and Mormon Church (CBS News Sunday Morning), 1987 January 11 (Video 3)
    Mormon men who died of AIDS and effect on their families. 14:00.
- Mormon Church and Equal Rights Amendment (ERA), 1980; DVD (Disc 57)
  - Sonja Johnson on Phil Donahue, 1980 January 16 (Video 1)
    Sonja Johnson, excommunicated Mormon feminist, discusses ERA on Phil Donahue talk show. 24:00.
  - Barbara Smith on Phil Donahue, 1980 January 16 (Video 2)
    Beverly Campbell, LDS Church spokeswoman, give rebuttal to Sonja Johnson on Phil Donahue talk show. 47:43.
- WBBM news story - Louise Degn, reporter, 1973; DVD (Disc 58)
  - Skiing in Utah, 1973 January 08 (Video 1)
    Comparison of skiing in Utah and Wisconsin. 03:53.